You know her?
She's one of the girls I killed.
TEDDY: Whoever's
looking for her.
we need to figure
out who that is.
Oh. I'm Victoria. by the way.
Reed Thompson.
ALEJANDRO: You'll be ready
to purchase another 25 keys?
(beep. line ringing)
LUCIA: No problem.
We'll be in contact.
Since when do we care
what Gustavo wants?
I made him a partner.
(moaning)
Papa? I've got to
tell you something.
Niggas broke into
my spot. tie me up.
and hit me with a
motherfucking baseball bat.
(groans)
SWIM: You see that?
You see those rocks?
- It's my new favorite.
- I ain't never seen that before.
- Fuck is that?
- Our future.
(funk music playing)
♪♪
Y'all cutting that
shit too small. man.
♪♪
♪ Keep going. keep going
♪ A-keep going
♪ Don't you give
up. keep going ♪
♪ Keep going. keep going
♪ Don't you give
up. keep going ♪
♪ Keep going. keep going
Man. we've been at this
shit for like a hour.
Can't we get some
bitches to do this?
Already did.
Nigga got jokes.
We should be out there
hustling right now.
No. no. no.
We're not selling this batch.
We gonna give it away.
What? For free?
Motherfucker. you
done lost your mind?
Man. how we supposed
to get paid. man?
Avi called this shit garbage.
Threw it in my face. Why?
Because he don't
know what it is.
Nobody in L.A. knows
what it is. not yet.
Ain't a market for it.
So... we gonna create it.
This motherfucker
talking about markets
like he Dow Jones.
Y'all weren't there. This
ain't no regular high.
One taste from this shit.
motherfuckers be feenin'.
And when they do. you tell
them to bring their cash
to MLK Park tomorrow. all right?
So. uh...
you're gonna let us sample the
product this time. right?
I mean. this ain't coke. We
gotta gain a little knowledge
if we're gonna
educate the masses.
Just tell 'em it's good.
Yeah. but I wanna know how good.
♪ And if you move your body
like you move your hands ♪
♪ Then I know you can
move your feet ♪
- Fine.
- Really?
On you.
But develop a taste
for that shit.
and you can go back to moving
furniture to make your ends.
Man. my couch humping days are over.
Don't worry 'bout me.
What you think? This will work?
I don't know.
♪ I said get up. get up... One
small step for man. right?
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Sit back down (lighter clicks)
♪ Right up on. we're
gonna funk you ♪
♪ Right on up. funk
you (flame sizzles)
♪ Right up. we're
gonna funk you ♪
♪ Right on up (lighter clicks)
♪ I say get up. get up.
get up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Get up. get up. get up. get
up. get up ♪ (exhales deeply)
♪ Get up. get up. get up
♪ Sit back down
♪ Right on up. we're
gonna funk you ♪
♪ Right on up. funk Oh...
Let's see that shit.
(gasps) Fuck.
(coughs)
Shit.
Holy fuck.
Oh. man.
♪ Yoda-lay-hee-hoo
Oh. fuck.
Yo. I'm good. (clatter)
♪ I said get up. get up.
get up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Get up. get up. get up. get
up. get up ♪ (laughs. coughs)
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Get up. get up. get up. get up.
get up ♪ We gonna make bank.
♪ Sit back down
(pouring)
- MAN: (shouts) Order up!
- WOMAN: Thank you.
MAN: Uh-huh. (dishes clatter)
(bell dings)
(sighs)
Relax. Mm.
Everybody in L.A.'s at least 10
minutes late for everything.
Thank you for coming with me.
Seriously?
Finding Kristin could
mean finding Jess.
Right.
(door bell jingles. door opens)
(door closes) MAN: Order up...
(sighs)
You got some way of
contacting him or...
Mnh-mnh. just his name.
Mm. Jim Stewart.
Wait. what? Ooh...
Sorry. it's just...
Jimmy Stewart?
(door bell jingles. door closes)
Oh. my God.
Wait. do you think it's a scam?
I don't know. I mean.
could be a coincidence.
(groans) Sh...
- Hey...
- MAN: 24. order up.
(sighs)
(imitates Jimmy Stewart)
"The money's in Joe's house.
"Right next to yours.
"And the Kennedys' house. and Mrs.
Macklin's house. too.
and a hundred others."
"And a hundred others."
(both chuckle)
I'm sorry. Oh...
I love Jimmy Stewart.
Are you a fan?
Oh. no. at heart. I'm more
of a Cary Grant girl. so...
Hmm.
(man speaks indistinctly)
(sighs) Oh. gosh.
Do you wanna keep waiting or
should we get out of here?
Fuck it. Let's just...
Let's go. okay?
(door bell jingles)
Oh. God.
(British accent) Hello?
(door closes)
Ah. I can see the resemblance.
Are you Jim Stewart?
Yeah. Yeah. it's in the
nose. in the eyes.
Faces worth remembering.
Wait. um. so you
really knew Kristin?
Well. don't know if
I'd go that far.
We partied one night.
Right. There was an Asian
chick there as well.
She had fake bits. Brilliant.
Okay. can...
So where was this? Some club.
Don't quite remember the name.
(sighs)
I might be able to
remember better
if my tourist visa
wasn't expiring.
Wait. what?
Money to hire a lawyer.
That would almost
certainly jog my memory.
I reckon a few thousand should do it.
(Sighs)
(sips)
She had a dimple on her chin.
and she did a mean Bonnie Tyler.
just in case you think
I'm not for real.
Wait. But...
I mean. I don't have a
few thousand dollars.
I do.
I got more in the car. I keep
it there for emergencies.
Come on.
(door bell jingles)
Now you're doing me a
real favor here. mate.
If I just get this
visa sorted. then...
Sure. It's in the trunk. So...
then I can gig again.
It's a... it's... it's a punk rock thing.
(keys jangle)
Now I'm right at a vanguard of this...
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
You are a special kind of piece of
shit. aren't you? (Bone snapping)
Fuck! Tell me the name
of the club right now
or I'm gonna break your
fucking arm. Jimmy.
(bone snapping) All
right. all right!
It's the Glitter Club.
(groans) Fuck.
(whispers) Wow.
(birds chirping)
Gustavo.
Nice boots.
I see we're taking
good care of you. hmm?
I bought them for him.
His old ones had holes in them.
Yeah. well. Lucia.
Siempre tan linda. huh?
(sniffs)
Your father's in the study.
He's been askin' for ya.
Okay.
Don't take too long.
He needs his strength.
I haven't seen you
in a couple of days.
Yeah.
I've been busy.
(speaks Spanish)
(door closes)
(knock on door)
(knocks)
(chain clacks)
Hey.
(exhales)
I've been calling you.
What's wrong?
The camp was hit.
When?
Early this morning. Elena?
- I don't know yet.
- The coke?
You think I give a shit about
the fucking coke right now?
Right. sorry. I...
I'll. um. I'll ask around.
I'll see what intel
I can scrounge up.
No. no. I'm going
down there. Teddy.
Right now. We both should.
(sighs)
What?
Does Club Glitter
mean anything to you?
(breathes sharply)
(exhales) All right.
look. don't worry.
Just... you go. I'll stay here.
I'll make sure she doesn't
get any further than that.
(breathes sharply)
I thought approaching her
was a bad idea. but...
you were right.
Look. if you're gonna go
down there. be careful.
The whole area's
probably still hot.
And the last thing I need is
you getting yourself killed.
I will.
Thanks. Teddy.
(breathes sharply)
♪♪
♪ So 1. 2. 3 Yeah! Get that!
KEVIN: It's like that. uh.
"Prince and the Pauper" nigga.
Them old motherfuckers from
back in the day. man. you know?
But except ain't no price.
It's just a rich white boy
from Wall Street. right?
And he get tricked to
switch places with Eddie
by these other crusty old
rich white guys. right?
And Eddie becomes a
Wall Street dude. man.
And the Wall Street dude.
he turn poor and shit
and they start treating
whitey like he a nigga.
Shit crazy. man.
And then. Eddie on the
floor pretending like
he ain't got no legs and
the police come over. man.
and they start. "Hey.
man. what are you doing?"
And he's like... Nigga. I
was with you. all right?
We saw that shit. like. two
weeks ago with Franklin.
Really? Are you sure?
Oh. yeah.
Hear y'all giving
away some new high.
He got you.
Hey. hold up. Hold up.
hold up. hold up.
Spread the word. all right?
Tell everybody.
Hey. man. um. how many of these
we give away? Like... like 30?
- Nah. more like 10.
- Really?
Ain't given away
30 rocks. nigga.
You sure?
Really?
Hey. wh-what you
all giving. man?
Something new and improved.
Shit. hit me with a couple.
Nah. nigga. you getting one.
(chuckles) Let me have two. man.
Hey. cuz. I said you're
getting one. all right?
Now you can come back
tomorrow and pay $10.
(scoffs) All right.
(spits) Hey. hook this nigga up.
All right. come here.
Who's that? What's up?
We got that new high.
He gonna hook y'all
up when he done.
Hey! Hey. man. Hey. Leon! Leon!
Come on! Come on!
Calm down. bitch!
- Hey! Hey. Leon!
- The fuck off me!
(shouting indistinctly)
- Get the fuck off my homie!
- Whoo!
Hey. kick his ass!
Get... hey. man.
these my new Adidas!
- Hey. let go of my leg. man!
- Hey. what the fuck you doing?
- Get him off me. Leon!
- Get the fuck off his leg.
Man. these my new Adidas. cuz!
Get off me. man!
♪♪
(sizzling)
(inhales deeply)
(exhales)
We have to talk.
About what's gonna happen
with the business.
Always so impatient.
Ever since you were little.
(chuckles)
I remember one time your
mom was doing cemitas.
You wanted one. but she said no.
That evening. she
was doing the wash.
And she sees you coming
out of the kitchen
wearing these old.
dirty overalls.
(laughs)
I've never worn overalls.
(laughs) Mm.
She stripped you right
there in the hallway.
Two cemitas come tumbling out.
(both laugh)
Oh... the reason I remember is
you said that extra cemita
was for your sister.
I know it's hard
to let someone in
after what happened
to this family.
Mija.
you're smart.
innovative. fierce.
But you can't do it alone.
You need people that
you can count on.
That's what helps you prosper.
That's what makes a life.
(crying)
(sniffles)
("Words to My Song"
by Dry Bread playing)
(indistinct conversations)
♪♪
(woman whoops)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Uh. you take the bar.
I'll take the floor.
Okay.
♪ Someone took the
words to my song ♪
♪ The next time I write a song ♪
♪ There ain't gonna
be no words ♪
♪ Let the music go on
♪ Oh. yes. I will
♪♪
(sighs)
♪ Oh. yes. I will
Hey. Hi.
Any luck?
No. you?
No.
(women chattering)
Fuck.
You know. I really thought there
would be something here. right?
I'm sorry. It's okay.
Come on. you wanna
get out of here?
(chattering. laughing)
(sighs)
(funk music playing)
(man exhales)
No.
Let's get shitfaced and dance.
♪♪
Yeah. I don't dance. Come on.
I seem to remember
Stewart getting down
in "It's a Wonderful Life."
Or does your impression
just end at the voice?
Bartender. uh. we'll
have a shot over here.
What do you want? Um.
anything but tequila.
Oh. I'd love a shot of tequila. please.
MAN: Coming up.
♪♪
(glasses clink)
Oh!
- Another round.
- You got it.
♪♪
(soul music playing)
Price point's right.
We won't have to sell to
white folks or Mexicans.
We sell it right here.
and. uh. same as weed.
But for big paper.
That takes care of your
problems with yeyo. right?
How big?
You would know big.
Off a single key.
the way we cut it.
we make 50... Selling nickels.
But it catches on and we set
the market. we sell dimes.
$100.000 off a single key?
Uh-huh.
And people be coming back.
Try if you want.
Oh. fuck that.
Nah. I've been with fools into freebase.
That shit is nasty.
All I know is. this
will catch on.
And when it does.
we could be makin'
seven figures a month.
♪♪
All right. We'll give your
little shit away for right now
and we can see how it go.
(claps hands)
(laughs)
(laughs) Thanks. Unc.
- See you. Aunt Lou.
- Bye.
(door opens) Hey. if it do pop off
the way that you're thinkin'.
it's gonna make some noise.
You thought about what
you're gon' tell your mama?
I'm thinking on that.
Keep thinkin'.
(doors creak)
(lock clicks)
Franklin gon' do this
with or without us.
Be better for him
if we in on it.
What? You trying to protect the boy?
(bag rustles)
We got a good life
here. don't we?
(rustling) Damn.
Yeah.
But it still ain't
enough. right?
♪♪
When I was a little
girl in Baton Rouge.
we ain't had no TV. but
we had this big 'ol radio
with a record player on top.
And that mug would transmit
all the way from Chicago.
WLS. (Laughs)
And on Sunday nights. they
would play live big band.
And I would imagine the women
in their evening dresses
and the men in their tuxedos.
And. baby. I wanted more than
anything to be in that room.
You sound like a
little girl right now.
Maybe I do. (clatter)
But seven figures a month. baby.
this world will be whatever
the fuck we want it.
♪♪
(laughs) Yes! Mm!
Yes! Mm!
Yes! (laughing)
(horse whinnies. blusters)
No. no. no. no. no.
(speaking Spanish)
(chuckles) Hey.
What are you doing out here
skulking like a thief?
Just took a walk.
Mira. Pedro. Take him.
I'll catch up with you. okay?
(horse whinnies. blusters)
If I had known you'd been
around. I would've invited you.
You ever been riding at night?
I've never been riding. señor.
- Never?
- Never.
What kind of a Mexican are you?
(both laugh)
Your father never took you?
(horse blusters)
Hey. papa. dale. dale.
He still around. your father?
No. señor.
What happened?
Killed.
When I was young.
Sorry to hear.
(horse blusters)
(whistles softly)
There is nobody. señor.
Well. at least you
still have us. huh?
Do think you need
some riding lessons.
(both chuckle)
(speaks Spanish under breath)
(horse blustering)
BRIGHT MOMENTS: ♪ Ooh! Is ya
funkin'. baby. is ya funkin' ♪
♪ Aye. is ya funkin'.
baby. is ya ♪
♪♪
♪ Aye. is ya funkin'
♪ Baby. is ya funkin'
♪ Baby. is ya funkin' tonight
Hey. Hey!
- I can help you.
- Good. Thank you.
I can help you.
♪ Tonight
No. I...
Hey. You're looking for
Kristin. right? What?
- You're looking for Kristin?
- Yeah.
- Let's go talk. Let's go talk.
- Okay.
♪ Move it all over
♪ I want to funk you
all night. girl ♪
♪ Stroke it down. do
it with feeling ♪
Of course she was here. I was
the one who invited her.
See. we had just started
doubling up in class
and she was my partner. and this was
the week... Wait. Class? What class?
Uh. you know. aerial
dance. the art of trapeze.
No. I was wondering if...
Wait. so were you guys hanging
out that night. or...
Yeah. Well. well. I was working.
but she was partying. though.
She had to blow off some steam.
you know. because of Nate.
That fucking asshole. I told her that...
So what happened then?
Did she leave alone or...
Um. no. but she met some
guys and left with them.
Guys... What guys?
I don't know. One kind
of had like a faint
frat-holey thing going on.
The other one was really hot.
Kinda looked like a heavier
Latino Freddie Mercury.
Okay. so who were they. though?
Do you know their
names or anything?
No. just that they were
going to keep partying
at the frat-hole's place.
And they asked me to go
and I was going to. but then I pulled my
left quad... So where were they headed?
What was the address? Um. I...
you know what?
I might've written it down.
That's possible. Coming through.
Let's see...
This is a disaster.
What does that say?
Oh. no. no. no. no.
(papers shuffling)
No. I don't know.
♪♪
Oh. my God. That
guy's such a creep.
I'm so sorry. I. like.
never write anything...
Oh. my God. Wait. no. no. no.
(gasps) Fuck me sideways
with a tire iron. That's it.
That's it? Yeah. that...
that's it!
Oh. thank you! Wow! (Laughing)
- Oh. my God!
- Okay...
- Wow.
- I never write shit down!
Can I take this? That's in...
This has never
happened to me before.
Thank you. Yeah. wow. I
hope you find Kristin.
Yeah. She's like... she had the
best straddle whip in class.
Thank you. And she always
brought me Skittles.
Yeah. thank you. And I
thought that was so sweet.
Thank you so much.
Bye. guys. Bye!
You know what? I gotta use the restroom.
Whatever.
Just two minutes. I'll meet
you by the front door.
Okay.
Don't take too long. Uh...
♪ Come back alone
♪♪
Hey. it's MacDonald. Uh.
listen. I need you...
♪♪
(camera shutter clicks)
(lowered voice) I don't know.
As long as it takes.
Please just do it.
Thank you.
(coins drop)
♪ He had the groove
♪ Had the groove
♪ That makes you move Excuse me.
Yeah? Uh...
Can I have these drinks? Thanks.
♪ That makes you wanna get
down. down. down. down ♪
♪♪
(sighs)
(mutters indistinctly)
(gasping)
♪♪
♪ Disco beat
(coughing) (ashtray clatters)
(retching)
(grunting)
(vomits) (crowd gasps)
Ah! What the fuck. man?
(grunts)
(shouting indistinctly)
- Back off!
- Shit!
- (shouting continues)
- Okay. okay!
Are you okay?
I think I need you
to take me home.
(song ends)
(insects chirping)
Tio.
This used to be a sitting porch.
You used to love to play here.
Your father moved out all
the furniture... (snip)
turned it into this.
It makes him happy.
It gives him peace.
You make him happy.
(speaking Spanish)
Uh-huh. You should talk. then...
about how you see everything moving
forward in this business. (Snip)
I'm not sure I understand
what you mean.
Well. you know. you're
bright. ambitious.
I'm sure you have ideas. (snip)
You know. changes that
you might want to make.
How you see things
into the future.
(snip)
Pedro told you. didn't he?
Of course he told me. (snip)
(door opens)
(door closes)
(footsteps approach)
(speaks Spanish)
I think you should stop
sleeping in the stash house.
You have some money now.
Get out of that shithole and
go find your own place.
Okay. Okay.
TEDDY: I got it. I got it.
(Victoria sighs)
(lock clicks)
So it's just there. um... Shit.
There on the right. Oh. shit.
oh. shit. oh. shit. shit.
If you... would you grab
me that medical kid
when you're done?
Yeah. I got it. okay.
- It's just under the seat.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. okay.
(keys jangle)
(breathing heavily)
(toilet flushes)
(breathes sharply)
(oven door creaks)
(whispers) Okay.
Here you go. Oh. thanks.
Oh. God. Oh. fuck.
I need some water.
Uh...
(groans. exhales)
(water running)
(thud)
(groans)
(exhales)
That's your nephew?
Um...
no. actually.
Oh. you're married?
We're separated.
How long?
I'm sorry. do you
mind if we don't...
Yeah. no. sorry. Of course. I
shouldn't have asked. Just...
(sighs)
Okay. (Inhales sharply)
(glass thuds) Are you
gonna be all right?
Yeah. I think I'll live.
Okay.
Hey. thank you so
much for everything.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna head out.
Wait. where are you goin'?
What do you mean?
I just. uh. you know. we
both had a lot to drink.
And. um. it's probably just
safer for you to crash here.
I'll sleep on the couch. No. I'm
gonna go to that house. Reed.
It's like 1 in the morning.
I don't give a fuck
what time it is. okay?
She said that they host late night parties.
(unlocks door)
All right. all right.
all right. just...
I'm gonna just change real fast.
And...
No. I really think
that you should rest.
Hey. we're in this together.
Right?
Okay.
Hurry up!
You know he crazy. right?
(laughing)
(alarm honking in
distance) (chattering)
(basketball hits
backboard. dribbling)
(hip-hop music playing faintly)
♪♪
- What's up with it?
- How's shit goin'?
Told you. nigga.
Fat-ass hobo pulled
a knife on me.
Oh. shit. Got his blood all
over my fucking kicks. man.
Damn.
You good. though? Yeah.
he ain't stick me.
But you're gonna reimburse
me for these shoes. though.
(laughs) Yeah. sure.
Give you 50 cents. you can walk
your ass down to Goodwill.
Man. fuck you.
Your mama dress you
up your whole life.
but I gotta pay for my own shit?
Hold up. you for real?
Real as death. nigga.
And I want a little extra to
pay for my frayed nerves.
Hazard pay.
It's fair. Saint. I mean.
we are putting our lives on
the line for this thing. man.
You wanna talk about
lives on the line?
I almost died twice since
I started this shit.
Man. this nigga full of excuses.
but you ain't nothing but
a cheap ass motherfucker.
(laughs) You get poked one
time by some junkie ass blade.
What about me? I've been
robbed. beat. shot at.
You wanna talk about hazard pay.
where's my hazard
pay. motherfucker?
You know what? Fine.
You want money? Here.
take some money.
Man. who done all the fucking
killing for you. man?
Step the fuck back. But now
you're some king or some shit?
You gonna tell me how to
wipe my own fucking ass?
I said step the fuck back! Hey.
(sighs)
- Fuck...
- Hey. man. Hey. what the...
Hey. man. What are
y'all doing. man?
Hey. hey! Come on. man.
(grunting)
Give me what you owe me.
you square ass Mama boy!
Get the fuck off me. you
jailbird motherfucker!
Hey. hey. hey... Fuck you.
bougie-ass motherfucker!
- Hey. fuck you...
- Hey. be cool. man!
Hey. back... Hey. back up. man!
Cool out. man!
Hey! Cool out. man!
Y'all acting like some bitches.
Fuck!
(dog barking in distance) We're
sitting on a silent fucking gold mine
if y'all don't fuck it up! Man. fuck you!
And fuck all this shit. man!
Man. I don't have to be
babysitting y'all. man.
Leon Sim is the man with the
fucking plans. huh? Ah. fuck you!
(groans)
Come on. Le! Le!
Leon?
(dog continues barking)
TEDDY: Quiet neighborhood.
(car door closes)
(breathing heavily)
VICTORIA: Just do...
Dang it. (dials call box. beep)
Hello? Is anyone there?
(call box squawks)
Hello?! Whoa. whoa. hey.
What?
Okay. um...
Great. (grunts)
Now we're trespassing.
It's okay. Well.
then. don't come.
Oh. no. no. getting shot would
be the perfect end to this day.
Hope they don't have a dog.
(lights click on)
Excuse me?
What do you think you're doing?
Oh. sorry. Hey.
this is your house?
Yes. and it's private property.
I'm sorry. Uh. all
right. this is...
I'm looking for someone...
My sister.
She went missing a couple weeks
ago and somebody told me
that she went to a
party at this house
the last night that
anyone saw her.
A party here?
The only kind of parties we
throw come with birthday hats
and kids under 9.
I have a photograph.
Do you... Do you recognize her?
No. And as sorry as I am
to hear about your sister.
I want you to leave. or
I'm calling the police.
Yeah. okay. Hey...
Of course.
Sorry for bothering you.
So. look. if you
remember anything else.
my name's Reed Thompson.
It's in the book. Of course. Mr.
Thompson.
(whispers) The
robe's a nice touch.
(normal voice) Thank
you for your help.
(crying)
(exhales) I miss her so much.
(exhales)
(cries)
Trapeze class? I mean.
what was she gonna do?
Run off and join
Barnum & Bailey?
(sniffles)
I don't know. I guess I just
didn't know her anymore.
(crying)
(sobbing)
- (humming)
- You all right?
Mnh-mnh.
Uh. nah. man.
Our world ain't on
fire anymore. huh?
Feel like a tiny animal
gnawing at my brain. man.
Yeah. probably best to leave
that out the sales pitch.
Yeah. you right. (baby
crying in distance)
Heard from Leon?
No.
No worries. He'll come around.
Man. come on. He always do.
Like that time you bought the
same exact shirt as him.
He always come back and eat pie
at the end of the day. right?
(speaking indistinctly)
FRANKLIN: Eat pie?
(men shouting indistinctly) Yeah. you
know. like. eat pie. Humble pie. Humble.
(cheering)
Oh. you wouldn't know
nothin' about that.
(laughs)
(basketball dribbling.
shouting continues)
You think they here for us?
(chuckles) Yes. they are.
MAN: Come on. man!
Breakfast time.
ladies and gentlemen.
Who's first?
(speaking Spanish)
You fucking piece of shit!
(object thuds)
You have the balls to come in
here after running to Daddy?
Look at this place.
You two have really put
your work in. huh?
I'm not sure that this is how I
would've done it. but. uh...
Looks good.
Anyone else here?
Gustavo?
I don't know where he is.
You tell him about
our discussion?
'Cause if I find out you
lied to me again...
He doesn't know anything.
Good.
Let's go here and.
uh. have a talk.
(keys jingling)
(knocking)
Hey. Saint. You home?
Hey. my nigga. My bad about
yesterday. all right?
Open up if you in there.
Come on.
(knocks)
(knocking) Come on. Saint.
(clicking)
Let's squash all this.
(pounding on door) Come on. man.
(scoffs)
(speaks indistinctly) was fun.
but this business. all right?
Mnh-mnh. That ain't cool.
You know I good for it.
It's 10 or nothing. sweetheart.
I don't make the rule.
Get you free Frosties for life.
Frosties?
Do you think I got this body
tossing back milkshakes. huh?
Finish what you got. man.
I'm-a head back to the crib
and restock. all right?
- All right. I got you.
- Back in 20.
- Cool.
- Baby. you ain't listenin'.
I done my shift. I
pay you double.
Walk away. Mama.
This ain't no credit
union. bitch.
(scoffs)
Or I tell your mama.
What's up. man?
Thank you. thank you.
♪♪
(doors creak)
(beads clack)
(sighs)
(turns off faucet)
(glass clatters)
(groaning)
Leon.
(door bangs open) Leon!
(breathing heavily)
Motherfucker caught
me slippin'. man.
(grunts)
(breathing raggedly)
I'm... I'm calling an
ambulance. all right?
Wait. Wait. (Gasping)
(door opens and closes)
Hello? I need an ambulance.
My friend's been shot.
- 1127 West 56th.
- (gasping)
(receiver clatters)
I called them. They on they way.
They on they way. It's
gonna be all right.
- (whispers) The crack.
- Hey.
- The crack.
- What?
The crack. the crack. The crack.
The crack.
Fuck. fuck! Fuck!
(beads clacking)
I'm coming! Aah!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Aah!
(beads clacking)
- (breathing heavily)
- I'm coming. man!
I'm coming out!
(panting) I got it.
(gasping)
Shh. shh. Hold on. Hold on.
They on they way.
They on they way. man. huh?
- They on they way.
- I don't wanna die.
You're not gonna die.
You're not gonna die. Shh.
Okay? (siren wailing
in distance)
- Fuck.
- You're not gonna die.
(gasping)
(sirens wailing)
(siren whoops. brakes squeal)
(car door opens and
closes. radio chatter)
MAN: You guys got everything?
(car door closes)
(car door opens)
(police radio chatter)
(siren wailing in distance)
♪♪
Captions by VITA...
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm